Contact

jperkins616@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jasmine-perkins-msn-rn-cmsrn-8753b0ba (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership Grant Writing Professionalism

Languages

English

Honors-Awards

Macy's Go Red For Women Multicultural Scholar

Texas Elks State Association Vocational Grant Program

Friendly Helper Award

Dean's List Scholar

Terry Scholar

Jasmine Perkins MSN, RN, CMSRN

Student Learning Specialist at Chamberlain University Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Leadership, Community Outreach, Time-efficient, Public Speaking, and Grant Writing. Strong education professional pursuing a Master's degree focused in Nursing Education and Health Informatics from Texas Woman's University.

Experience

Chamberlain University
1 year 11 months

Student Learning Specialist August 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Professional Nurse Tutor August 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months) Houston, Texas Area

- Plan and lead individual and collaborative group sessions that encourage student engagement and academic development
- Facilitate subject matter comprehension and practical application of key course objectives
- Engage a diverse student body comprised of a variety of ages, cultural backgrounds, ethnicities and academic preparation
- Help students build test-taking skills, study strategies and time management techniques as they complete their academic program and prepare for examinations (course, standardized, and professional/NCLEX-RN)
- Assist with assessing the academic needs, developing and documenting plans for remediation

Demonstrate comprehensive knowledge of subject matter and the essential elements assessed in NCLEX-RN exam

- Communicate academic progress of students to the Assistant Dean of Academic Success, documenting progress using TutorTrac®
- Demonstrate passion for education, student success, professional behavior and accountability in meeting service standards

Memorial Hermann Health System Registered Nurse July 2016 - November 2018 (2 years 5 months)

Memorial Hermann Northeast Hospital

Registered Nurse II

- Delivers safe and appropriate care to patients, according to the nursing skills inventory and the age and needs of the patient/population served
- Coordinates the planning for the delivery of nursing care with an interdisciplinary team and administers appropriate clinical decisions in the delivery of patient care
- Collaborates with, directs, and may delegate to the healthcare team in the attainment of positive outcomes based on data, research, evidence, and professional standards of care. Coordinates treatment plans; develops/ implements discharge and/or transfer plans
- Participates in a systemic, interdisciplinary, and ongoing evaluation of programs, process improvement and desired client-centered outcomes
- Considers the diverse needs of each patient through the entire continuum of care, providing and ensuring the highest level of service according to established service standards, optimizing the patient experience
- Promotes a safe and accountable environment; adheres to all Memorial Hermann policies, procedures, and standards, being a good steward of resources, including time management, supply management, productivity and quality of service
- Serves the dual role of clinician and educator, providing an individualized nursing orientation to the nurse's level of experience, while assisting with clinical orientation, focusing on competence, patient care content and unit culture

Tarrant County College Student Developmetal Coordinator June 2014 - August 2014 (3 months) Supervised student enrichment trips. Created and implemented leadership programs, presented collegian success tips about how to find funding for college. Critiqued and edited student resumes.

Education

Texas Woman's University

Master's degree, Nursing Education (2017 - 2020)

Texas Woman's University

Certificate, Health Informatics · (2017 - 2018)

Sam Houston State University
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2017 - 2017)

Lonestar College Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2016)

Tarrant County College
Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2014)